"It's a '57-facet
round brilliant pink."
"3.82 carat."
It's gorgeous.
"It's one of the most exquisite diamonds
we have."
It's such an unusual color.
It must be really expensive.
It's on the higher end
of our line, but...
Unique and very special.
Should we do it?
- We'll take it.
- Excellent.
I wish you every happiness
Mr. Cho, Mrs. Cho.
Honey, I love it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Sweetie.
Here you go.
She's a beaut.
- You all right?
- Yeah, just a little, uh...
- A little tickle in my throat.
- You sound like you're getting a cold.
- You should see a doctor.
- Oh, I don't need a doctor.
- Frauds in white coats.
- Whatever.
Just don't sneeze near me.
The last thing I need is a cold.
- Will do.
- We got a live one.
There's no question this diamond's part
of the stolen cache.
- Carat, cut, color all match.
- Let's go get the bad jeweler.
Why don't you go back
to my place, jump into bed?
I'll come tuck you in
as soon as we're done.
No, I'd rather be here with you.
- Is something wrong?
- F.B.I. the engagement's off.
"Six weeks ago, two security guards
were killed outside of Fort Worth."
"They were transporting half a million
dollars worth of diamonds."
What does that have to do with me?
The diamond you sold out
was part of the stolen shipment.
No. No, wait.
Six weeks ago?
I was out of the country.
In Barcelona.
- Wren will tell you.
- It's true. He was.
We don't suspect you killed
the man yourself.
- Not with those hands, you certainly didn't.
- But you planned it.
Or got the diamond from
the people who did.
I purchase the diamond I sold you
legitimately two weeks ago.
I bought many gems that day
from several dealers.
We'll need their names.
And the receipts.
I'm sorry. The receipts?
Little pieces of paper they give you
when you buy something.
Yes, yes, of course. I just don't know
what I can put my hands on.
We have a new office manager,
and everything is in disarray.
Isn't it amazing how easy it is
to spot an illicit couple?
And they always think
they're fooling everyone.
- It's just... I just think it's amazing.
- I assure you, that's...
Don't even try to defend yourself here.
Look at you, with your petite manicure
and your pocket square,
your spray tan.
Everything screams mid-life crisis
impending divorce
and sweet Wren's charming blush
tells us the rest of the sordid tale.
If you're planning on getting
a divorce, Mr. Joubert
you'd want to hide
your assets.
Is that why you don't have
any receipts?
I'm not getting a divorce.
That's ridiculous.
I love my wife.
- She speaks.
- Wren.
Take that back.
We are gonna need those receipts.
Word of advice... he cheated on her
he's probably gonna cheat on you
and I know that probably seems
very difficult to believe right now
but it's the way of the world, kid.
- Morning, Agent.
- Vega.
- How'd it go at the jewelry store?
- It went okay.
- Make any arrests?
- Nope.
- Got anything useful?
- Not sure yet.
Sir, I know you're angry
and I just wanna say again,
I am sorry for lying to you.
Abbott did not give me clearance to go
on the mission
and yet I said he had.
It's inexcusable.
Let me know what I have to do
to make it up to you and I'll do it.
Okay.
"Are you sure
you're all right?"
Oh, yeah. Just a little
lemon and honey for the throat
- and I'll be right as rain.
- You look pale.
Thank you.
Hey. Did you get the receipts
from the jeweler?
- Wylie's working on that right now.
- Okay, good.
Has your wife heard back from
the commerce department yet?
No, not yet, and she better
hear soon.
She's been waiting for months
wound tighter than a piano wire.
- Tell her I said good luck.
- Me, too.
You look pale.
Told you.
Wylie, where are we
with the jeweler?
Joubert jewelers has been
a family-owned business
for three generations...
no legal troubles.
- And what about Joubert's alibi?
- It checks out.
He was out of the country
until three weeks ago.
And, the story that he bought
the diamond legitimately?
It also checks out.
His receipts show that someone
named Josef Rosales sold him
$50,000 worth of diamonds
2 weeks ago
including several
Australian pinks.
- Who's Rosales?
- He's a vendor at a traveling gem show.
It... it's a, uh, gem market
that travels from city to city.
Vendors buy gems
in large quantities
and then sell them at the show
to retailers like Joubert.
- And where's this gem show now?
- Houston through the end of the week.
Well, why don't you head over
and talk to Rosales?
We'll hang back here
and work on the receipts
- see who else Joubert bought from.
- Sure.
Cho, why don't you, take Vega?
I'd rather take Lisbon.
Take Vega. She told me
what happened and apologized.
What she did was wrong,
but she's young.
And reformable, I think.
Vega, let's go.
Ye... yes, sir, right away.
Also on display is our blue
and purple Tanzanite
from Mount Kilimanjaro.
"This is a highly prized gem
due to its scarcity."
"Another color-changing gem
is the Alexandrite from Russia's..."
- You ever interrogate a suspect?
- I've done practice interrogations.
Then you haven't.
Follow my lead.
If you're not sure if you
should ask a question, don't.
Try not to lie to anyone.
- "We have several black opals in the back."
- Got it.
"These have a fire in them, trust me."
"Don't go by their name."
"And finally, sapphire,
the gem that..."
Our full cooperation.
Just let me know.
- Is something the matter?
- I'm Agent Cho. This is Agent Vega. F.B.I.
Kirk Upton.
- I saw your badge.
- Yeah, we're looking for Josef Rosales.
Josef. Yeah, his booth's right over there.
Is he in trouble?
- How well do you know him?
- Not really well.
I haven't really been
with the show that long.
Agents Cho, Vega.
Elon Bell, head of security.
I was told you'd be coming. Welcome.
- You think stolen gems are being sold?
- Is that why you're here?
Mr. Upton, give us some space,
if you don't mind.
Yeah. Sure. Sorry.
If someone's using the market
to sell stolen goods
that's of significant concern.
My bosses want me to help
any way I can.
We need to speak to some of your vendors
starting with Josef Rosales.
- Absolutely. This way.
- Thanks.
- "Hey."
- Hey. Lena. Hey, what's up?
I was gonna call, but I wanted
to tell you in person.
You got the call.
Bob Ackerman texted me
half an hour ago.
You are looking at
the next undersecretary
for the Department
of Commerce, baby!
Yes! Yes! Oh, baby,
I knew it. I knew it.
- Well, I'm glad you did, 'cause I didn't.
- No, no, no. See, you deserve this.
You earned this.
Because you're Wonder Woman.
We got to celebrate.
We got to celebrate big, too.
It's not a done deal yet.
I have to be confirmed,
and that could take months.
I don't care. I don't care.
You know what this is?
This is your chance
to make a difference.
I know. It's...
- I can't tell you how much I've wanted this.
- Oh, I know.
Ackerman wants to meet for drinks tonight
and talk about the vetting process...
- around 7:00?
- Absolutely.
Great.
Hey, Lena.
You're there, baby.
We're there.
- See you tonight.
- Yeah.
- Yes!
- Yes, I sold diamonds to Jacques Joubert.
He's a long-standing customer.
He purchases from me every year.
And this year you sold him
stolen diamonds.
- You think I'm stupid?
- Maybe. I don't know you yet.
You know what? Go.
Take your little F.B.I. badges...
I suggested he calm down.
Even if I wanted
to do something as stupid
as pass stolen gems,
it would be impossible.
Why is that?
The gems are registered.
They are accounted for.
How do you register a gem?
Every gem has a serial number
saying when and where it was mined
where and by whom
it was cut.
Every gem I sold Joubert
had that number.
If he had one that was stolen,
I don't know where he got it
- but it wasn't from me.
- We need to look at your records.
- I have customers.
- Not until you're done with us.
Secure the area.
I'll be right there.
Agents, can you check
something out with me?
"Very special gems
being featured."
"Somebody... We were
just coming around the corner."
It's that guy who approached us. Upton.
"Kirk Upton... 31 years old"
San Antonio native,
recently divorced, two kids.
- Any arrests?
- Uh, yes.
Two misdemeanors and a felony
"which didn't stick, none of it violent
all more than ten years ago."
What's he been doing lately?
Trying various moneymaking schemes
it looks like... none of them lasted.
Then how is Upton's murder
connected with the gem heist?
We don't know
but he did not sell Joubert
that pink diamond.
And he didn't have any
of the stolen gems in his booth.
"Of course he didn't
have any on him."
- He must have had a partner.
- "Why?"
"Because the gem heist
was engineered by a pro"
not someone looking
for career counseling.
Upton probably panicked
when he saw Cho and Vega
told his partner to confess or run.
Boom.
Who's the partner?
Well, let's take a look
at Upton's associates.
Lisbon, why don't you talk
to the ex-wife? Cho...
"Why don't you and Vega
talk to anyone and everyone"
"who came in contact
with Upton?"
Wylie, why don't you tap
into the security cameras
at the convention center?
See if you can find any footage
of Upton's movements before he died.
- Jane...
- Yeah?
- Go home.
- What, and miss all the fun?
Poor Kirk.
Good guy, basically.
Just could never figure out
what he wanted to do.
There was a new scheme
every month.
Eventually I had to get out
of the marriage.
There's only so many fresh starts
you can take.
What was his money situation?
Kirk was in a motorcycle
accident last year.
Doctors' bills?
Forget it.
Plus, our boy Pauly
is special needs.
Kirk was paying for his tutor.
Is that why he got into
the gem business?
He said some of those guys
make up to $100,000 a city
once they get going
but he never saw that kind of money.
Records show that Kirk has two
misdemeanor convictions and an arrest?
He hung with some bad guys
when he was younger.
But be involved in a gem heist?
Kirk just wanted to be a dad.
Did he ever mention any friends
from the gem show?
Someone named Lake...
No. Pond. Walker Pond.
This whole thing just kills me.
Any idea who could have done this
to him, Mr. Pond?
No. No, God, no.
Kirk's a...
Kirk was a sweet kid.
People liked him.
You worked with him?
I tried to help him.
Kirk's, uh...
He was always amped up
in a hurry.
I told him, "slow down."
You know, "you got to build your business"
but, he didn't hear me.
How does a gem seller go
about building his business?
You've got to learn the trade.
And that takes time.
Kirk wanted a shortcut.
Anyone else Kirk was close to
at the show?
I really don't know.
We only talked about business.
Did you talk to him today?
No. I got here late.
Anyone you might have seen him
talking to, however briefly?
Yes. I saw him a couple times
recently with Greta.
Seemed to me like they were
having an argument.
- And who's Greta?
- Greta Fortensky.
She's the gem show appraiser.
She's been here... 15 or so years.
- What's that?
- Vendors can't sell their gem
without first having an appraiser
tell them what it's worth.
Wylie. What's that?
Security cam footage
from the gem show.
- Live?
- No, it's from this morning.
- I was tracking Kirk Upton.
- Oh. Well, uh...
Possible to make it live?
I'd like to see what's going on there.
Sure.
Cool.
I'm contracted by the gem show
as an independent appraiser
which allows me to monitor
the show's integrity
which stays sterling because
I keep the vendors honest.
Their gems are priced
appropriately because of me.
Bibby, don't do that.
- Sorry, Mom.
- Come here.
My daughter Bibby
works with me.
I learned how to appraise
gems from my own mother
and Bibby will pick up
when I leave off.
It's nice to meet you.
I understand you and Kirk
might have had an argument.
No. He just thought I was
under-appraising his gems.
That happens a lot
with younger vendors.
- They dream of striking it rich fast.
- Which is not my problem.
What happens when a vendor thinks
he's being under-appraised?
We'll usually discuss it with them.
And after we do...
- my appraisal generally stands.
- Was Kirk Upton angry?
Kirk was never angry.
He was just sad.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
- Yeah?
- "Hey, Cho. Your fly's open."
- "Jane, where are you?"
- The office. Where else?
- You're using the security cameras.
- Yeah, very good.
- And, who is it that Vega's talking to?
- Greta Fortensky.
She and her daughter
and appraisers.
You think you could, show me the...
the woman Vega's talking to?
Yeah, I think so.
She looks like a barrel of laughs.
- Think she's the killer?
- I don't know yet.
Well, looks like
she's got it in her.
- "You think?"
- Sure. Look at that posture.
I would bet money she has a riding crop
hidden in the closet somewhere.
"And her daughter looks like
she'd like to give you an earful."
Who are you talking to?
- He's talking to Cho.
- Cho.
- Oh. May I?
- Oh. Yeah.
Hey, Cho, hang on for a second.
I want you to hear this.
Put it on speaker.
Wylie, what did you get
on Upton's movements?
He left his booth after talking to
Cho and Vega
according to the map...
of the convention center
the person he visited
was... Walker Pond.
- Pond? You sure?
- Yeah. Why?
Well, Pond told us he hadn't
talked to him today.
Well, talk to him again
and see if his story stands.
Yep.
I'm, I'm just gonna...
- Whoa, I'm getting the spins.
- Hey, why don't you go home?
Yeah, just go home and
I'll get someone to drive you.
Yeah, uh, that... that could be a good idea.
Hang on one second.
Think he's running?
Bell.
We're looking for the vendor
who works that booth...
- Walker Pond. You know him?
- Pond, sure.
He packed up in a hurry
about 45 minutes ago.
- Didn't say why.
- He's running.
- Anything I can do to help?
- No, we got it.
I'm gonna get Houston P.D.
to put out BOLO.
Call Wylie, tell him to start tracking Pond.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Excuse me, sir? Sir?
We got a hit
off Pond's credit card.
He bought gas at a station
outside Galveston.
Galveston.
What was he doing there?
Well, I checked, and Pond was
in the Air Force stationed at Galveston.
Okay, so what did he do?
He monitored planes
to and from South America.
So you think that he's trying
to leave the country?
I think he might be.
There's a plane leaving
for the Yucatán at dawn.
- Cho and Vega... they're in Houston, right?
- Yeah.
Okay, so, uh, it's
a 45-minute drive to Galveston.
Tell them to go to the airport
and sit and wait for that plane to leave
just in case Pond arrives.
- Okay.
Lena, everyone
at Commerce is delighted.
- You were our first choice.
- Well...
I'm gonna choose
to believe that, Bob.
All right, let's dig in.
- Talk about getting you confirmed.
- Here we go.
Well, it's not you.
The other side, well they just
want to stop the administration
from accomplishing anything.
They will use whatever
they can against you.
- We're ready.
- Good.
So Lena's résumé is impeccable.
No problems there.
We've got some people following
your paper trail.
So far, so good.
What about your personal lives?
I have to ask.
- There's nothing to tell there, Bob.
- We met college.
Married 17 years.
Never been happier.
- All right.
- Well, okay.
What about you, Dennis?
- What do you mean, what about him?
- Well, I'm not being confirmed here.
Well, you're part of the package.
You've had an exemplary career.
Some good talking points there.
What can you tell me about
Rio Bravo station?
- Wow, you have a file on me, too.
- Wouldn't be doing my job if I didn't.
Right. Oh, well, Rio Bravo
was a joint task force... F.B.I., D.E.A.
We were taking down the cartels
near the border.
I was on the job about a year.
Did good work,
took down some bad guys.
Dennis is really proud
of the work he did down there.
Going after the cartels is tough.
- It's tricky.
- Yeah.
Dirty war.
Hard to tell the criminals
from the cops sometimes.
Anything to talk about?
- No.
- Nothing?
Absolutely not.
We're all good here.
All right.
- Well, I'm starving.
- Me, too.
- Let's eat.
- Thank you.
Sir, I appreciate you inviting me
to work on this case with you.
It wasn't my idea.
Abbott made me do it.
I did apologize.
I understand what I did.
It's about trust, okay?
If we're gonna work together I need to be
able to trust you with my life.
Now an apology is easy.
Trust is earned.
Just tell me how.
It's Pond.
F.B.I.! Stop!
Okay, okay. I didn't...
- I didn't know it was you.
- What do you think you're doing?
- I thought you were the other guy.
- Who? What other guy?
- Do you know who that is?
- His name's Losa.
Vega, stay here. Get Galveston P.D.
down here. I'm gonna go find this guy.
Okay.
No!
Stop!
Get your hands in the air!
I said get your hands
in the air.
Off the ladder. Now.
Okay. Stop.
Do not move. I said stop.
Stop... I will shoot...
Name's Uriel Losa.
He's muscle for
a Fort Worth loan shark.
Pond apparently owes a lot.
Now Losa didn't know
we were F.B.I.
He thought we were there
to collect from Pond for someone else.
So why did he start shooting?
Said he was just trying
to scare us away.
- What happened there?
- Dealing with Pond. It's nothing.
Minor sprain.
Job well done, you guys.
Both of you.
Whatever you got to do
to me, go ahead.
It's my fault.
Why is that, Mr. Pond?
Because I got Kirk killed.
- How exactly did you do that?
- My business was off.
So I borrowed money
from Losa's boss.
A lot of money.
And I was having trouble
paying it back.
Why not just throw him
a few rubies?
Yeah. That's what
he wanted, too.
I had to draw a line.
I owed him money.
I wasn't gonna hand him
my career, too.
But he sent Losa after me.
- But he killed Kirk instead.
- Why would he do that?
I let Kirk borrow my hoodie
that morning.
You know, and we...
we had the same color,
same build...
So Losa must have thought
Kirk was me.
And when Kirk went out
that fire exit, he killed him.
Why was Kirk using the fire exit
to begin with?
To have a cigarette.
It's some secret
smokers' area that...
Kirk went out there at least
six times a day.
Losa must have followed him out.
I hate to burst your bubble
but Uriel Losa was nowhere
near the convention center
- the day Kirk Upton was killed.
- Seriously?
We tracked him.
He was 30 miles away.
He had nothing to do with it.
Still, it was a nice try.
"You know, I almost hated to tell him."
- "He had it all worked out."
- Yeah, I know what you mean.
A guilty conscience
is a terrible thing to waste.
In the meantime, we've got nothing
and the gem show ends tonight.
"Well, not completely nothing."
Pond said Upton was a smoker?
Well, I think that tells us
who's behind all this.
- "Certainly how I can get a confession."
- How?
- There is one problem.
- "What?"
Well, I'm... I'm a little sick.
I'm not... I'm not sure
that I can do it.
- So what are we gonna do?
- Well, you could do it.
- Me?
- Sure.
You've seen me do this
sort of thing heaps of times.
I have no idea what you're gonna say
but I'm pretty sure the answer is no.
Why don't you come by the Airstream
and I'll explain it to you?
- Why can't you just tell me now?
- Because I'd like to see you.
"And I was hoping you would
bring me some soup."
- Fine.
- Tomato or bean, please.
I got it.
No, it's... it's cool.
It's like the red badge of courage, only tan.
- The tan badge of courage.
- It's nothing.
Look, you brought the guy in.
That's something.
Well, it wasn't enough.
Cho will come around.
- Hey, Bob.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
- No problem. What's this all about?
- Let's talk a walk.
- Sure.
You asked if there was
anything in my work
with Rio Bravo that could
be problematic. Now...
Let's just say,
what if there was?
Well, then that's gonna be
a problem for Lena.
- No, she had nothing to do with it.
- Of course not.
But we need squeaky clean.
If the optics start to look bad
well, we may have to look
for someone else.
Okay. Then what do I need to do?
You know how hard she worked for this, Bob
and I really want her to have this.
All right, look.
As long as you're in the picture
you're potentially an issue.
But if you're not a part of the picture
if there's some distance...
What good is that gonna do?
I'm still her husband.
If, for instance, we can put out the word
that you and Lena are going through
a trial separation.
- Are you serious?
- She won't have to say a word.
We just have to make sure
the other side hears it.
It might convince them
to leave you alone.
- No. I can't do that.
- All right.
You want a way to fix it,
and I'm suggesting a way.
Let me know when you decide.
Yes, Lisbon?
So, do you think you can do this?
Jane walked me through it.
I think I can.
She'll have an earphone
and I'll be talking to her all the time.
I'll be able to see everything
that's going on.
She's gonna be fine.
And what do you need?
I need Wylie to monitor
the security cameras with me.
Hello, Lisbon.
- "Can you hear me?"
- Yes.
Well, you look good.
Very convincing.
I cannot believe
you talked me into this.
Oh, you're gonna be just fine.
I'm right there with you
"inside that head of yours."
- I'm gonna throw up.
- Me, too.
Pre-show jitters.
Always get 'em.
Good afternoon.
Little louder.
My name is Teresa Lisbon.
- I'm a psychic medium.
- Good.
I work as a special consultant
with the F.B.I.
As many of you already know
we're investigating a gem heist
"and the murder of two security guards"
along with the murder
of one of your colleagues...
Kirk Upton.
The person behind all this
is in this room right now.
Using my gifts
I'm gonna reveal
who that person is.
They're hooked.
Yes, I will unmask
Kirk Upton's killer...
very, very soon.
What do you got?
Let's try her.
I got nine hits here.
I'm gonna need a little time
before I can get the right one.
Okay. Lisbon, you mind,
stalling for a minute?
Would anybody...
like to ask me a question
before we begin?
Lots of people. You.
There's no such thing
as psychic powers.
Disagree.
- I... I disagree.
- What's my star sign?
Come on, you gotta sell it, Lisbon.
Make 'em believe.
I'm sorry. The spirits won't listen
if there's any negative energy in the room.
Now you're cookin'.
Got her... Mary Kate Barrows.
Okay. Lisbon, you're gonna be
talking to someone called...
Mary Kate Barrows.
"Just like we practiced, okay?"
I'm getting something.
Is there someone named Mary
in this room?
- Middle name Kristina or Kathy?
- Kate?
Mary Kate. Last name...
your last name,
it's two syllables. It's...
- B-b-b... Barrows.
- Yes.
Mary Kate had a Havanese
called Roger that just died.
- What's a Havanese?
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
- It's a little dog.
- It's a dog called Roger.
Oh, my God.
Mary Kate, Roger...
He wants to say hi and that he's okay.
- He can talk?
- Well, yes, of course.
All of God's creatures can talk
in the afterlife.
Move on while you're ahead, Lisbon.
Time to lay the gaff.
I'm getting something else, people.
I'm... I'm hearing another voice right now.
It's a man voice.
Kirk. Kirk? Is that you?
Yes!
"I will speak on your behalf."
Kirk says he was working
with his killer.
They were selling stolen diamonds
for the gem show.
"Kirk?"
Kirk.
Tell us who did this
to you, Kirk.
Wait, Kirk... he wants to speak
directly to his killer.
He says, "Shame on you."
"He thought you were friends."
Everyone's on the edge of their seat.
Keep going, keep going. The smoking bit.
Wait, I-I can't... I can't hear you, Kirk.
You got to speak louder.
Smoking? Wait, wh-what does
smoking have to do with this?
He says, "I hope they have
a lot of nicotine gum in prison."
Tell us, Kirk.
Just give us one name.
He says he'll tell us.
But he wants the killer's mother
to guess first.
He wants the killer to see
the shame in her eyes.
God. Kirk's murder? You?
- Bibby...
- Stay out of it, okay?
You got 'em, Lisbon.
Now close the deal.
If the killer identifies themselves
they'll get a deal with the F.B.I.
If not, I'll find them myself.
No deal.
- Baby, don't be stupid.
- I'm not stupid! Mom!
I'm smart!
And I can do whatever I want
with my life because it's mine!
It's not yours! It's not Kirk's!
It's mine.
Bibby, please!
Kirk and I ran into each other
one night at a bar.
He had just gotten divorced.
We had a few drinks.
One thing led to another.
We realized that we both needed money...
him for his kids, and me...
to get away from my mom.
So we came up with a plan.
I knew when the gems would arrive
from the U.S. buyers that I had
gotten to know over the years
and Kirk knew someone
who could pull off a heist.
"Someone who also needed money."
"A friend from his teenage years."
- "So Elon Bell stole the diamonds."
- Yes.
No one was supposed to die.
When Bell killed those two guards
Kirk freaked out.
But by then, it was...
It was too late.
"Once I got the gems"
"I used my cover
as an appraiser."
"I switched the vendors'
registered gems"
"with the stolen ones, and then I sold
the vendors' gems on the black market."
- And then we showed up.
- Yes.
Kirk wanted to come clean.
And I said he we should
discuss it.
"But there was
no discussing it."
Everything I had been holding
inside just came out.
I couldn't stop it.
That woman didn't really
talk to Kirk, did she?
Of course not.
So how did she know I was
chewing nicotine gum?
Mother like yours isn't gonna
let you chew bubble gum.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
It was just a long day,
that's all.
Well, I've been looking houses
for sale in Georgetown
and they're not as expensive as you think.
I mean, they're expensive,
but they're beautiful houses.
Look, Lena...
I don't think I wanna go to D.C.
You know, I have a good unit
here, seniority
and I don't want to give
those things up.
- What?
- We can be a 2-city couple, right?
- Dennis, stop.
- No, no, no. Other people do it.
- I think it's...
- This is about Rio Bravo, isn't it?
Now I never asked you
what happened down there
and you didn't wanna talk
about it, and I respected that.
But I can't do this anymore,
not if you're acting like this.
- Lena, I can't.
- Baby, it's me. You can tell me anything.
- No, trust me, it needs to be this way.
- Why?
Because you're going to be
asked questions
and if any of those questions
involve Rio Bravo
then you need to be able to say
that you don't know anything about it.
You need that, Lena.
Now, we'll see each other
on weekends and holidays.
You're gonna be working
seven days a week anyway.
It's probably better that I live here.
- Sir, could you please stand up?
- Why?
I'm gonna fall
and I want you to catch me.
- What?
- Then I'll do the same for you.
- No.
- It'll just take a minute.
Vega, you fall right now,
you're gonna hit the floor.
- Well, it's a trust exercise.
- I know what it is.
Well, we did them all the time in training.
They really work.
I'm sure it did in Quantico,
but not here.
Then what do I do?
- I mean, I have to do something.
- Do your job.
- I understand.
- Good.
Vega.
I'm going to the firing range tomorrow
after work. You wanna come along?
- I'd like that.
- Good.
"You need to get some sleep."
You were very good.
Very good.
We were very good.
It was fun, talking to all those people
with you whispering in my ear.
I'd do it again.
What if we just left?
Just took off?
Like, on vacation?
No.
Just leave.
Go someplace different,
move on.
- Well, what do you want to do?
- Oh, I don't know.
But are we really gonna work for the F.B.I.
for the rest of our lives?
Look at dead people,
chase bad guys?
- It's who I am, Jane.
- I know.
Just thoughts.
Just thinking.
Good night.
- I'll come and check on you tomorrow, okay?
- Okay.
Good night.
Sorry.